[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What substance do South American Indians use on the tips of their poison darts?", "correct_answer": "curare", "incorrect_answers": ["ammonia", "Metrazol", "snake venom"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "British musician, singer, and songwriter Elvis Costello was born Declan Patrick Aloysius MacManus.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Eve of Destruction, Eves creator had a teenage fantasy that Eve attempted to fulfill in a bar and motel in California.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Johnny Crawford was once a Mouseketeer for Walt Disney.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ants communicate through pheromones.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of animal is the serval?", "correct_answer": "Feline", "incorrect_answers": ["Canine", "Ungulate", "Reptile"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In The Longest Day, Private Steele becomes deaf because his parachute is caught on a church steeple and is very close to the bells. Who portrayed this parachutist?", "correct_answer": "Red Buttons", "incorrect_answers": ["Eddie Albert", "Mel Ferrer", "Richard Beymer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following words is related to phobias?", "correct_answer": "Irrationality", "incorrect_answers": ["Strength", "Genetic", "Popularity"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What toxic chemical was released in the Tokyo subway by the Aum Shinrikyo sect in 1995?", "correct_answer": "Sarin", "incorrect_answers": ["Strychnine", "Sulphur trioxide", "Sodium cyanide"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mark the incorrect statement about sequoias, which are among the largest and oldest trees on the planet.", "correct_answer": "Sequoias can reach up to 150 m (490 ft) in height.", "incorrect_answers": ["Sequoias are evergreen trees.", "Sequoias are monoecious trees.", "Sequoias can live for more than 2000 years."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Del Griffith", "correct_answer": "Planes, Trains  Automobiles", "incorrect_answers": ["Class Reunion", "Uncle Buck", "Ferris Buellers Day Off"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Back to the Future, when Marty is in the diner in 1955, he asks for what kind of drink?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["something without sugar", "Tab", "Pepsi free"]}]